Inventory of the Alexander Brown Papers (1) 1815-1910
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Papers of R. L. Brown, the son of Alexander Brown, 1842-1870, n.d.
  - Manuscript volume containing the accounts of Robert L. Brown, 1867-1868., Approximately 70 pages. Remainder of pages torn out. MsV. 9 (Box 10)
  - Ledger from "Union Hill," 1 Jan. 1874-1886., MsV. 10 (Box 10)
  - R.L. Brown's ledger of the Lynchburg Female Seminary, 1860-1866., MsV. 11 (Box 11)
  - R.L. Brown's ledger of the Lynchburg Female Seminary, 1867-1870., MsV. 12 (Box 11)
  - Manuscript volume containing the accounts of Robert L. Brown, 1860-1867., Approximately 202 pages. MsV. 13 (Box 11)
    Manuscript
    Manuscript Includes:
    Notes on shipping to Virginia, 1606-1625, listing name of ship, dates of sailing and arrival, captain, etc.
    Manuscript copies of A True and Sincere Declaration &c, 1610. (a copy made in the British Museum for Brown)
    Virginia Reviewed by George Donne, 1637
    The Discourse of the old Company of Virginia, 1625. (printed in Virginia History Society Magazine, 1893-1894)
    and A Short Collection of the Most Remarkable Passages from Origin to the Dissolution of the Virginia Company(London 1651).
  - Includes miscellaneous accounts of R.L. Brown. (Box-folder 11:116)
  Series 11: Page Proofs
- Page proofs of the books written by Alexander Brown.
  - Page proofs of The Genesis of the United States., MsV. 14 (Box 12)
  - Page proofs of The Genesis of the United States., MsV. 15 (Box 12)
  - Page proofs of The First Republic in America., MsV. 16 (Box 13)